-嘿  -嗯  好啦  当然
- Hey.  - Yeah. Yeah, okay. Sure.
我们能不能谈谈
Look, can we talk about
昨晚这里的发生的事
what happened here last night?
行  先给我几秒钟
Sure. Just give me a second
让我进入你那愤怒又诡异的状态
to get all huffy and weird like you.
你敢相信某某人在昨天晚在这
You believe that whoever did something last night
做了某某事要么没做某某事  有没有搞错
did what they did or didn't do? Come on!
你真不了解我说的是什么
Okay, you really don't know what I'm talking about?
-不知道  -好  昨天晚上的派对之后
- No.  - Okay. Last night, after the party...
我看到瑞秋在你家的阳台上
I saw Rachel kissing that jerk
亲她那个混蛋同事
from her office out on your balcony.
在我家阳台  真的吗
Our balcony? Seriously?
这可好玩了  我就和莫妮卡说
That's so funny. I told Monica
我们应该在阳台上加个灯的
we should put lights on our balcony
可她说不用  外面那么冷  没人会去
and she said, ''No, no. It's too cold.
然后我说
Nobody will go out there.'' And I said:
要是我们加个灯或许就有人会去了
'Maybe if we put some lights out there they will.
对  我过来就是要和你谈这事
Right, that's what I came over to talk about.
我看到瑞秋在你家阳台上亲了一个男人
I saw Rachel kissing some guy.
虽然那里连灯都没有
on your balcony, even though there were no lights!
那你要跟她谈谈吗
So are you gonna talk to her?
为什么  为什么我要
Why? Why should I?
如果她要找寻新生活  没关系
I mean, if she wants to move on, that's fine.
这么说没关系  真有说服力
You know when ''that's fine'' sounds true?
喷着口水用力吼
When someone yells it and spits.
不  我认真的
No, I'm serious.
如果她想要跟别人约会
I mean, if she wants to date people,
没关系  我不在乎
fine. I don't care.
但是至少她要跟我说啊
But at least she could have told me.
我已经完全不顾个人生活
You know, I've been putting my life on hold
集中全部精力在艾玛身上了
and concentrating on Emma.
但如果她想要出去随便亲男人
But if she wants to go out there kissing guys
那我也要去
she barely knows, then so will I.
真好笑  罗斯是同志
Very funny! Ross is gay!
没  很好  所以你也要有新的生活了
No, no. Good, so you're moving on.
你准备怎么过新生活
Do you have any idea where you're moving on to?
我机会多的很呢
I've got plenty of opportunities.
就刚刚在咖啡厅里  有个女人对我笑呢
Just now, there was some woman at the coffeehouse smiled at me.
还有一天在地铁  有个女人
And then the other day on the subway, a woman
不小心  坐到我的手上了
''accidentally'' sat on my hand.
老兄  别跟我炫耀你疯狂的单身生活了
Dude, don't rub my face in your crazy single life.
还有  在学校有个人类学家
And there's an anthropologist at school who totally came on to me
跨部门餐会的时候 不停勾搭我
during the interdepartmental potluck dinner.
我为什么要结婚啊
Why did I get married?
《老友记》  第九季 第13集  莫妮卡唱歌记
Friends S09E13 The One Where Monica Sings
问你们一个问题
Hey, let me ask you guys something.
我明天要拍新艺术照
I'm having new headshots taken tomorrow.
摄影师说
The photographer said she thinks
我应该修修眉毛
I should have my eyebrows waxed.
男生修眉会不会很怪
Is that weird for a guy?
-嗯  那要看情况  -什么情况
- Well, it depends.  - On?
看他的变性手术做到哪个阶段了
On how far along he is in the sex-change process.
不  我完全不同意
No, I totally disagree.
我觉得男生那样做没有什么
I think it's fine for a guy to do something like that.
尤其是演员
Especially an actor.
我不是说你有那个必要  你的眉毛…
I mean, not that you need to. Your eyebrows are....
你们别这样  别盯着我看  吓着我了
Stop it, you guys. Stop staring, you're freaking me out.
你手指头也毛茸茸的
Your knuckles are kind of hairy too.
天啊  现在我还要除这些毛吗
Oh, man, now I have to get those done too?
哇  你要做的改造可不少啊
Wow, talk about high maintenance.
你还不是染发
You dye your hair.
-我是女人啊  -双重标准
- I'm a woman.  - Double standards!
差点忘记 你今晚去迈克的钢琴酒吧吗
Before I forget, are you coming to Mike's piano bar tonight?
只要不让我上台唱歌就去
Only if I don't have to get up and sing.
但是大家都要唱歌啊  很好玩的
But everybody sings. It's so fun.
上次有个可爱的老先生上台
Last time, this adorable old man got up there,
歌词全忘了  糗呆了
forgot all the words, flipped out
然后大家就嘘他下台  太好玩了
and everyone booed him off the stage. It was so funny.
我不是很会唱歌
Look, I'm not good at singing.
怎么啦  你害怕了
Oh, what's the matter? You scared?
怕我唱的比你好吗
You afraid I'm a better singer?
怕我会用歌声把你打得落花流水
You afraid I'm gonna beat you at singing?
不是  这招对我没用
Nope. Nope. It's not working on me.
哇  我一定是长大了
Wow, I must be growing up.
好吧  就过来支持迈克就好了
Okay, fine. Just please come and support Mike.
你不需要唱歌
You don't have to sing.
所以我又不用唱歌
So I don't have to sing,
而且还可以坐在那里评论别人
and I can just sit there and pass judgment on others?
-还可以一边喝酒  -我要去
- While drinking.  - I'm there.
你们好 我需要你们的帮忙
Hi, you guys. Listen, I really need your help.
我想我做了一件很蠢的事
I think I did something really stupid.
是  瑞秋  但至少结果还是很漂亮的
Well, yes, Rachel, but you got something so beautiful out of it.
不  不是那件事  我昨晚亲了盖文
No, not that. I kissed Gavin last night.
-我的天  -你亲了他
- My God.  -You kissed him?
对  就在派对结束之后 我们在阳台上
Yeah, it was after the party, we were on the balcony
等等  我一直都在家
Wait, wait, wait. I was at home the whole time.
为什么没看到
How did I miss that?
派对才刚结束 你可能正忙着烫平包装纸
Well, it was the end of the party. You were probably ironing wrapping paper.
哦  没错
Oh, yeah.
那你们怎么会亲起来的呢
So how did you end up kissing?
我们单独在一起  然后他又很体贴
We were all alone and he was being really nice...
然后又送我这条围巾
and he gave me this scarf.
我以为你讨厌他
I thought you hated him.
看来爱与恨之间只有一线之隔
Well, there is a thin line between love and hate...
而结果  那条线就是这围巾
...and it turns out that line is a scarf.
你想要跟这男的交往吗
Are you thinking of starting something up with this guy?
不知道  太复杂了  我和他一起工作
I don't know. lt's so complicated. I work with this guy.
我已经有小孩  还有罗斯
I have the baby, and I have Ross.
我不知道该怎么办
I don't know what to do.
而我再十分钟就要进办公室见到盖文了
And I have to be at the office and see Gavin in 10 minutes.
听起来你应该想想
Sounds like you need to think about
要怎么跟盖文说了
what you want and talk to Gavin.
而且你一定得要跟罗斯谈谈
And you definitely should talk to Ross.
或者…
Or...
我可以打电话请病假  那就都不用管了
...I could call in sick and not deal with it at all.
请了五个月的产假  才回去上了四天班
Wow! Five months maternity leave, you're back for four days...
亲了一个同事  又要请病假
kiss a co-worker and call in sick.
他们有你这个员工真幸运
They are lucky to have you.
-嗨  -嗨
- Hi.  - Hi.
我预约了修眉
I'm here for my eyebrow appointment.
什么姓名
Name?
钱德勒·宾
Chandler Bing.
好的  很好
Okay, very good.
请先坐一下  宾先生
Have a seat right here, Mr. Bing,
桑妮亚很快就过来
and Sonya will be right with you.
好的  谢谢
Okay. Thanks.
我碰了下那玩意儿
I touched the stuff.
让我来处理
I'll take care of it.
谢谢
Thanks.
来你们… 你们这里的男生多吗
So do you...? Do you get a lot of guys in here?
-当然  -太好了
- Oh, absolutely.  - Oh, good.
你想认识认识吗
You looking to meet somebody?
好了  我们开始吧
All right, let's just do this.
好的  我们等一下再上热蜡
Okay, we'll get to the wax in a minute.
首先我要先拔一些杂毛  好吗
First, I want to tweeze some of the strays, okay?
这可能会有点痛
Now, this may sting just a little bit.
你随意  我可是一点都不怕痛的
Please, I have an extremely high threshold
妈妈咪啊   喔  我的脸  我的脸
Holy Mother of God! Oh, my face! My face!
我没事  我没事  我没事
I'm all right. I'm all right. I'm all right.
只是有点吓到  没什么
It's just a bit of shock, that's all.
-但是我没事  你可以继续了 -好的
- But I'll be fine. You can go again.   - Okay.
抱歉
Sorry.
可恶  你这女人
Damn it, woman!
全纽约最适合结婚的单身汉来了
It's the most eligible man in New York.
新生活进行得如何呢
How's the moving on going?
不太好  地铁上又有个人坐到我的手
Not well. I went on the subway again and someone did sit on my hand...
但是这个人既不是女性 也没有穿内裤
but that person was neither female nor wearing pants.
或许你完全错估情势了  我是说你想想看
Maybe you're going about this the wrong way. I mean, think about it:
单身白种男性  离婚三次
Single white male, divorced three times,
有两个非婚生子女
two illegitimate children.
你应该要自己心里有数的
The personal ad writes itself.
真是好笑  是啊
You know, that's funny. Yeah.
那你觉得你这辈子会找到工作吗
So do you think you'll ever work again?
你在干嘛   你知道我们会斗个没完的
What are you doing? You know I can only dish it out.
我不敢相信瑞秋就这样抛下过去
I can't believe Rachel just moved on
而且还什么都没有跟我说
and didn't say anything to me.
或许她并没有抛下
Maybe she didn't move on.
或许那只是冲动之下吻的
Maybe that kiss was just an impulsive,
过生日才发生一次的那种
one-time birthday thing.
不  一个月以前  她还把电话号码
No, a month ago,
留给一个在酒吧认识的男的
she gave her number to some guy in a bar.
她有跟他出去吗
Did she go out with him?
没有  他打电话来时
No. When he called
我把留言扔了
I threw the message away.
真是厉害啊
The high road.
你知道吗  够了
All right, you know what? Enough.
抱怨够了  我要展开新生活了
Enough talking. I have to get moving.
瞧瞧那两个金发美女  跟我一起过去
Hey, check out those two blonds over there. Hey, come with me.
你要害每个人都离婚吗
Are you trying to get everybody divorced?
不是让你真泡妞
You don't have to do anything.
但是我们两个一起过去会比较好
It'll just be easier if it's two of us.
就像大学一样  记得吗
Like college, remember?
你先过去说笑话热场面
First, you break the ice with some kind of a joke
让她们知道你是好玩的人
so they know you're the funny one.
然后我再插入有趣的话题
I swoop in with interesting conversation...
让她们知又道我才是既聪明  有教养还性感
so they'll see that I'm the brilliant, brooding, sexy one.
我还以为笑话都是我来讲
I thought I got to make the jokes.
你不用上班吗
Don't you have to be at work?
拜托  走吧
Oh, come on.
你们好  我叫钱德勒
Hello. Hi, my name's Chandler.
这是我朋友罗斯
This is my friend Ross right here.
我们在想
We were wondering
如果你们加入
if you're up for it,
我们就只差六个人来玩人体金字塔了
we only need six more people for a human pyramid.
接手  接手
Swoop. Swoop.
我注意到你在看报纸
Hey, I notice you're reading the paper.
欧洲又有水灾了  对吗
Another flood in Europe, huh?
问你们个问题
Here's a question:
你宁愿被淹死还是被活活烧死
Would you rather drown or be burned alive?
-很抱歉  我们要走了  -好的
- I'm sorry, we're just leaving. - Okay.
宝刀未老
We still got it.
谁
Who is it?
盖文  我带一些汤来给你
Gavin. I brought you some soup.
-为什么   -我听说你生病了
- Why? - I heard you were sick.
喔  对  等一下 让我先整理一下
Oh, right! Hold on, let me just clean up in here a little bit.
你好  盖文
Hello, Gavin.
今天上班好想你  你还好吗
I missed you at work. How you feeling?
不想对你说谎  我病得很重
I'm not gonna lie to you, I'm pretty sick.
那就好  因为我还担心
Oh, good. Because I was having a totally paranoid moment
你是在装病逃避我
where I thought you called in sick to avoid me.
不是  不是
Oh, no, no, no.
我昨晚很愉快
So I had fun last night.
我也是
So did I.
你的病到底传染性有多高呢
Exactly how contagious is this thing you have?
是因为站在阳台上受凉了
Is it a cold from standing on the balcony,
还是被猴子咬了呢
or did a monkey bite you?
-只是单纯的感冒  -有发烧吗
- It's just a cold.  - Do you have a fever?
让我看看
Let me see.
怎么  怎么了  怎么回事
What? What is it? What's the matter?
那张照片  罗斯在对你做什么
What's Ross doing to you in that picture?
他在用化石刷子帮我除尘
Oh, he's dusting me with a fossil brush.
他觉得那样很好玩
He thought it would be funny.
-是啊  -是的
- Right. Right.  - Yeah.
-罗斯  -是啊
- Ross. - Yeah.
你们之间有什么吗
What's the deal with you guys?
我不想当第三者
I don't wanna get in the middle of anything.
你不是第三者
You're not getting in the middle of anything.
别担心罗斯
Don't worry about Ross.
快躲  是罗斯  躲起来
Hide! That's Ross! Hide!
躲起来
Hide! Hide!
但是你说不用担心
Yeah, but you said not to worry
我撒谎  而且我也没有生病
I lied and I'm not sick either!
躲到窗廉后面
Just stay behind the curtain!
-嗨  -是莫莉啊  不是罗斯
- Hi.  - Oh, Molly. You're not Ross.
不是  我来接艾玛到你妈家  记得吗
No. I'm here to take Emma to your mother's, remember?
对  是的  是的
Right. Yes, yes.
-千万别慌  -怎么了
- Don't panic.  - What?
有个男人藏在你家窗帘后头
There is a man behind your curtain.
我皮包里有防狼喷雾
I have Mace in my purse.
不  没关系  不用
No, that's okay! No, no, no.
那是我同事盖文在发神经
This is my business associate Gavin being silly.
出来吧  别站那
Come out from behind there.
你好  我叫盖文  很高兴认识你
Hi. Gavin. Pleased to meet you.
是我要站在那里的
It was my idea to stand there.
-你好  我去带艾玛  -好的
- Hello. I'll just go get Emma.  - Okay.
那么…
So...
为什么我要躲呢
why did I have to hide?
我以为那是罗斯
I thought it was Ross.
如果真是又如何
So what if it was?
我以为你们之间已经没有什么了
I thought there was nothing going on between you.
是没有  完全没有
There isn't. There totally isn't.
你听到钥匙转动的声音
You hear keys in the hall
就像斗牛第一次出栏一样跳了起来
and you jump like a bronco coming out of the chute for the first time.
我做过牛仔小丑
I used to be a rodeo clown.
好的  听着  盖文
All right, Iook, Gavin
我觉得是  你在这里让我有罪恶感
I guess I felt guilty that you were here
我也不想的
which I shouldn't.
罗斯跟我没又有在交往
You know, Ross and I are not in a relationship
但他是我孩子的父亲  而且我们住在一起
but he is the father of my child. And, you know
再加上  我们有太多过去了
we do live together. And plus, there's just so much history, you know?
只是…  我不知道
It's just-- I don't know.
我很抱歉  脑子很乱
I'm sorry. I'm just all over the place.
没关系
It's okay.
这或许与我无关
It's probably not my place,
但是我可以给你一个建议吗
but can I give you a piece of advice?
好的
Yes.
你应该跟罗斯谈谈这件事
I think you should talk to Ross about all this.
大家都这样说
People keep saying that.
我很抱歉  盖文
I'm sorry, Gavin.
别抱歉
Don't be.
只是现在不是好时机
It's just bad timing.
讲真的吗  牛仔小丑
So seriously, rodeo clown?
技术最棒的  小姐  技术最棒的
One of the best, ma'am. One of the best.
没有时间留给失败
"No time for losers,
因为我们是真正的冠军
'cause we are the champions of the world...!"
谢谢
Thank you!
她是我女朋友  大家不用这么做
Oh, she's my girlfriend. That's not just how we do it here.
我要休息一下  回来时
I'm gonna take a little break, and when we come back
肯尼将要演唱《自摸》
.we've got Kenneth singing ''I Touch Myself.''
我就不做评论了
I'm not here to judge.
你一定要上台唱
You have got to sing.
不  我告诉过你我不行
No, I told you I can't.
你会很喜欢的  而且你的嗓子很好啊
But you would have so much fun. And you have a really nice voice.
你什么时候听过我唱歌
When have you heard me sing?
常常  当你在煮饭的时候
All the time, when you're cooking.
-什么  -是啊  你总是哼哼着
- What?  - Yeah, you're always singing:
好吃  好吃  好吃 我肚肚里有爱爱
Yummy, yummy, yummy I've got love in my tummy
是啊  那个我还挺拿手的
Yeah, I do rock that one.
你难道一点都不想要上去唱吗
Isn't there just a little part of you that wants to get up there?
一点而已  老天  好可怕
Just a little. But, God, it's so scary.
我根本不知道要唱什么
I don't even know what I would sing.
嗯  我有歌本
Well, I've got a book around
《德耳塔·道恩》
''Delta Dawn.''
我不得不注意到
Hi. I couldn't help but notice,
你的项链好特别
but that's an unusual necklace.
你一个小时前就来搭讪过了
You already hit on me an hour ago.
没错  所以确定不行吗
Right. So that's a firm no?
不敢相信  我一直被判出局
I don't believe this. I just keep striking out.
我也不敢相信
I don't get it either.
我是说  很明显地你是很饥渴了
I mean, you're obviously desperate.
你问女人想怎么死
You're asking women how they wanna be killed.
太棒了  瑞秋继续去亲男人
This is great. Rachel's gonna keep kissing guys
直到找到她想要的男人 而我将孤单地死去
...until she finds the one she wants, and I'm gonna die alone.
是淹死还是…
By drowning or...?
他为什么要跟我分手
Why would he break up with me?
我不知道  亲爱的
I don't know, sweetie.
我要的只不过是爱他  希望他也爱我
All I ever wanted was to just love him and have him love me back.
我有这么不可爱吗
I mean, am I so unlovable?
-哇  -我懂
- Wow. - I know.
好了  以上是肯尼所带来的
All right. That was Kenneth with his
现场演绎的《自摸》
much too literal rendition of ''I Touch Myself.''
接下来是莫妮卡演唱
Coming up next, we've got Monica singing
《德耳塔·道恩》
''Delta Dawn.''
等等  我不能在这些人面前唱
Wait. I can't sing in front of all these people.
假装他们不在  没关系的
Just pretend they're not even here. It's okay.
聚光灯一打到你身上  亮得耀眼
Once that spotlight hits you, it's so bright,
你也看不到任何人
you won't see anyone anyway.
我叫莫妮卡  我要唱的是《德耳塔·道恩》
Hi, I'm Monica. And l'm going to be singing ''Delta Dawn.''
德耳塔·道恩  你手上拿的是什么花
"Delta Dawn, what's that flower you have on?
是随过去岁月褪色的玫瑰...
Could it be a faded rose from days gone by? ..."
你可以看穿她的上衣吗
Can you totally see through her shirt?
像X光一样
Like an x-ray.
今天不穿内衣可倒霉了
Bad day not to wear a bra.
带你一起去他天上的殿堂
"To take you to his mansion in the sky-y?"
我需要你的帮忙
I need your help.
看起来很严重
Wow, it seems serious.
出什么问题了  艾希莉·贾德
What seems to be the problem, Ashley Judd?
我要去拍艺术照  所以去修了眉毛
I'm getting new headshots taken. So I went to get my eyebrows shaped.
很抱歉  求你了  让我笑一会吧
I'm sorry. Moment to make fun of that, please.
我看起来可能有点娘  可还是能揍倒你
I may be a sissy, but I'll still pound you into the ground.
修眉太痛了  我只能让她拔一边  所以就
Look, it hurt so bad, I could only let her do one eyebrow, and now
两边不对称了
they don't match!
像毛毛虫宝宝在追妈妈
It's like a baby caterpillar chasing its mama.
你得帮我  好吗   我这有马克笔
You got to help me out, okay? Look, I have a magic marker.
帮我把细的这边画粗  照出来不会蠢
Fill in the skinny one so I don't look stupid for my pictures.
好的  但首先这是绿色的
Okay, first of all, this is green.
我他妈的该怎么办啊
What the hell am I supposed to do?!
我可以帮你
All right, I will help you out...
但是你要答应我  不会把我告诉你的事说出去
but you have to promise you won't tell anyone what I'm about to tell you.
什么事  什么事
What? What?
好了
Okay.
你知道大部分的小孩都是帮人除草
You know how most kids get their allowance
或是倒垃圾什么的来赚取零用钱
from mowing the lawn or taking out the garbage?
而我赚零用钱的方式就是
Well, I earned mine
帮我父亲还有他的"生意伙伴"修眉
by plucking the eyebrows of my father and his ''business partners.''
我的天
Oh, my God.
看来你不需要我的帮忙了  乔伊小乔妹
Yeah, well, I guess you don't need my help, Victor-Victoria.
不   我要  我需要你帮忙
No, no, no. I do. I do. I need your help.
但是钱德勒
But, Chandler, I don't know if I can
我不知道能不能再忍受拔毛  真的好痛
take any more plucking. It hurt so bad.
安啦  有我的冰块跟芦荟配方 加上
Not with my combination of ice cubes, aloe vera and my gentle.
温柔的连自己也厌恶的手法
self-loathing touch.
带你一起去他天上的殿堂
"To take you to his mansion in the sky-y?"
抱歉  可歌唱完了
I'm sorry, the song's over.
你有看到我在上面吗
Did you see me up there?
清清楚楚
Every little bit of you.
不敢相信我在大家面前唱歌
I can't believe I sang in front of people
他们还喜欢我
and they liked me.
你们有听到还有人大喊
Did you hear that guy shouting,
瞧瞧那些小费吗
''Look at those tips''?
tips:意同乳头
我有帮你多赚小费吗
I mean, did I really help you get a lot of tips?
当然有
Sure.
莫妮卡  不是说你唱得不好
Mon, not that you didn't sound good
不好
Good?
你没有听到他们的欢呼吗   我是太好了
Didn't you hear them? I was great!
谢谢你逼我上台
Thank you so much for making me do this.
这是我收到过最好的礼物了
That is the best gift ever.
还有什么是好礼物  内衣
Also a good gift: underwear.
谢谢你让过来
Thank you so much for letting me do this.
公共厕所让我觉得很恶
Public bathrooms freak me out.
我根本尿不出来  更别说其他的
I can't even pee, let alone do anything else.
但是更棒的是  你居然不介意说出来
But what's great is you don't mind talking about it.
这真是太神奇了
It is so amazing
在我跟艾瑞克分手的同一天  遇见了你
that I met you on the same day that Eric broke up with me
这就是  失之男友  收之新男友
because it's like, you lose a boyfriend, and you get a boyfriend.
你不用担心  这不是备胎疗伤法
No, don't worry. This is not some rebound thing.
我对艾瑞克已经完全没感觉了
I am totally over Eric.
挑得真好  罗斯
Good choice, Ross.
你在家
Hey. Hi. There you are.
我到处在找你
I've been looking for you everywhere.
是啊  我在家
Hello. Well, here I am.
我妈到九点才会把孩子带过来
My mom is not bringing the baby back until 9:00.
所以我希望  我们可以有机会来…
So I was hoping you and I could have a chance to kind of--
有人在这里吗
Somebody here?
是的  是蜜雪儿
Oh, yeah. That's Michelle.
谁
Who?
是我最近在约会的女生
Oh, just this woman I've been seeing.
你有在约会
You've been seeing someone?
是啊  我没有提过吗
Yeah, didn't I mention that?
其实  我们也没有约会多久
I mean, we haven't been going out too long...
但是我们之间有特别的火花
but there's this amazing connection between us.
而且在你进来之前  她叫我是她男朋友
I mean, in fact just before you came in, she called me her boyfriend.
我是觉得有点太快  但是觉得也不错
I thought it was a little too soon, but also, it felt kind of nice.
你用阿莫西林治什么呢
What are you taking amoxicillin for?
真是太棒了  你已经可以自在的
How great is this? You're already comfortable enough
翻看我的东西了
to look through my stuff.
抱歉  蜜雪儿  这位是我室友  瑞秋
I'm sorry, Michelle, this is my roommate, Rachel.
而且我也是艾玛的母亲
And I'm also Emma's mother.
艾玛是谁
Who's Emma?
我跟你说过  是我的女儿
I told you about my daughter.
这位是你女儿
This is your daughter?
我可以当你的新妈妈喔
I could be your new mommy.
好了
And done.
我的天
Oh, my God.
我根本都没感觉  你还找什么工作啊
I didn't feel a thing. Hey, are you still looking for a job?
你比那些个沙龙的臭娘们
Because you could tweeze circles around
拔得好多了
that sadistic bitch at the salon.
谢谢  想要看看吗
Thanks. Wanna see what it looks like?
好啊
Yeah.
完全对称了  很好看耶
They totally match. They look great.
看起来真棒  你好吗
They look great. How you doing?
是啊  我觉得看起来也挺不错的
Yeah, I think it looks pretty good.
我本来有点担心会
I was a little worried I was
让这上面的胎记露出来
uncovering a birthmark right about there
但原来那只是一点巧克力渣
but it turned out to be a little piece of chocolate.
钱德勒  真是感谢你
Chandler, thank you so much.
不用客气
No problem.
你看  我们刚做了一小时很娘的事
Listen, that was a pretty girlie hour we just spent.
现在应该做一些男人的事来弥补
We should do something manly to make up for it.
是啊
Yeah.
-给我夹个睫毛  -好啊
- Curl my eyelashes.  - Yeah!
下一首歌
For my next song,
我想唱比较轻快的  好吗
I think I'll sing something a little more upbeat, all right?
指针姐妹的《兴奋》怎样呢
How about the Pointer Sisters' ''I'm So Excited''?
弹得活泼一点哦
And make it bouncy.
嗯  你自己就可以办得到了
Well, you can probably take care of that on your end.
很抱歉我迟到了
I'm sorry I'm late.
等一下你看到乔伊  就知道为什么了
You'll understand when you see Joey.
亲爱的  你正好赶上  我要再唱一首歌
Honey, you're just in time. I'm about to sing another song.
真的  在大家面前吗
Really? In front of all these people?
他们很喜欢我
And they love me.
我的天
Oh, my God.
她是群众喜闻乐见的
She gives the people what they want.
好的  看好了
All right, watch.
今晚就要发生
"Tonight's the night we're gonna make it happen,
今晚我们将一切抛在脑后
tonight we'll put all other things aside.
这次屈服吧  让我看到你的爱意
Give in this time and show me some affection..."
那是我老婆的乳头吗
Are those my wife's nipples?
真是好玩  我之前怎么没有注意到
Isn't that funny? I didn't see that before.
要不然我不会让她上去的
I wouldn't have let her go up again.
得让她停下
I've gotta stop this.
管他的  他们还是爱我
Who cares? They still love me.
你  自摸的那个  出去
You, touching yourself! Out!
哇  她厕所去的真频繁
Wow! She does that a lot.
罗斯  你没告诉我你是博士
Ross, you didn't tell me you were a doctor.
等一下  你还没有告诉她  你是博士
Wait a minute. You haven't even told her you are a doctor yet?
你认识她多久了  一个小时吗
How long have you known her, like an hour?
事实上是一个半小时
Actually, about an hour and a half.
告诉过你不久  但我们之间有特别的火花
I told you it wasn't long, but there's an amazing connection between us.
你也有感觉到吗
You feel that too?
我以为只是我单方面而已
I thought that that was just me.
你开玩笑吗
Are you kidding?
你想要这周末一起去度假吗
Do you wanna go away this weekend?
再说
We'll see.
罗斯  这是怎么回事
Ross, what's going on here?
我们现在是可以带陌生女人回家了吗
Are we just bringing strange women back to the apartment now?
我不知道
I don't know.
那我们现在是可以在阳台上亲吻男人了吗
Are we just kissing guys on balconies?
你怎么会知道呢
How do you know about that?
通过神奇的眼睛
Through the magic of sight.
我在这里  哄我们的女儿睡觉
I was here, putting our child to sleep
艾玛
Emma.
当我从窗户看过去  就看到你在和男人接吻
When I looked through the window and saw you kissing a guy...
一个你认识有多久的男人  一星期吗
you've known for what, a week?
天啊  就因为这个吗
God, is that what this is all about?
你带她回来报复我吗
You bring her up here to get back at me?
不  事实上是我要尿尿
No, actually, see, I had to pee
在公共厕所里我又尿不出来
because I can't use public bathrooms...
因为有寄生虫
because of the doody parasites.
好了  蜜雪儿  你该走了
Okay, Michelle, it's time to go.
-那  打电话给我  -好的
- Well, call me.  - Okay.
等等  你没有我的电话
Wait, you don't have my phone number.
你知道吗  如果是命中注定  我会猜到的
You know what? If it's meant to be, I'll guess it.
再见
Bye-bye.
得分哦
Score.
你不喜欢她吗   我还希望我们可以
Did you not like her? Because I was hoping we could come
去参加你的阳台亲吻派对
to your kissing parties on the balcony.
不敢相信你竟然这么小题大作
I can't believe you are making a big deal about this.
只不过是一个吻而已
It was one kiss!
-跟一个人  就这么一次  -真的吗
- One guy. One time! - Oh, really?
-真的  -喔  真的吗
- Yeah. - Oh, really?
喔  真的
Oh, yeah.
-那个酒吧认识的男的呢  -谁
- What about the guy from the bar?  - Who?
你给他电话号码的那一个
The guy you gave your number to.
你是怎么知道的
How do you know about that?
因为他打来找你
Because he called here looking for you.
所以别跟我说  你只是亲了一次男同事
So don't tell me kissing this guy from work is a one-time thing.
因为你又在酒吧  又在阳台上
Because you've been out there in bars and on balconies
已经一个多月了
for over a month now.
你都没有礼貌性和我说一声
And you don't even have the courtesy to tell me.
-为什么我没有拿到留言  -什么
- Why didn't I get that message?  - What?
那个酒吧男的留言  为什么我没有拿到留言
From the guy in the bar? Why didn't I get that message?
因为我折起来放到裤子口袋里了
Because I folded it up and put it in my pants pocket.
你没有去找过吗
Do you not look there?
罗斯
Ross.
我没有拿给你
I never gave it to you.
为什么
Why?
我不知道
I don't know.
天啊  你知道吗  我不
Oh, God, you know what? I don't
你以为你是谁呢  你有什么权利决定
Who do you think you are? Who are you to decide
什么留言我该收  什么不该收
what messages I should or should not get?!
-我是谁  -是啊
- Who am I?  -Yes
我是在你去酒吧认识男人的时候
I'm the guy who's taking care of our baby...
在家照顾我们的孩子的人
while you're at bars meeting guys!
我真不敢相信
I cannot believe you.
我还希望能够跟你  成熟地谈谈我们之间
I actually came in here hoping to have a mature conversation with you about us.
但我不能跟会藏我留言
But I can't do that with someone who hides my messages
还会带疯女人回我公寓的人谈
and brings crazy women back to my apartment!
正常的人没有一个要跟我回来
Hey, none of the sane ones wanted to come back with me!
这不是重点好吗  重点是
That's not the point, okay? The point is
是你抛下我们的过去  而你却没有说
you are the one who moved on and didn't tell anyone.
天啊  罗斯  这真是糟透了
Oh, God, Ross, this is just so messed up.
我们是怎么了
What is wrong with us?
大家知道我们的情况后  都会问
When people hear about our situation, they ask:
你们住在一起  还不是夫妻
''You live together, but you're not a couple,
但是你们又有小孩  不是很奇怪吗
yet you have a baby? Isn't that weird?''
我会说  不会  我们都没问题
And I say, ''No. It's not, because it works for us.''
但是你知道吗  是有问题的
But you know what? This doesn't work.
事实上  还正好相反咧
ln fact, this is the opposite of working.
的确如此
Clearly.
你也知道
And you know...
我们有说过只要一切没问题
we said that we would live together
我们就会一直住在一起
as long as this makes sense
然而  或许一切不再是没问题了
and maybe this just doesn't make sense anymore.
是啊  或许不再是了
Yeah, maybe not.
那你想要怎样呢
So, what do you wanna do?
嗨
Hi.
我跟艾玛可以过来住一阵子吗
Can Emma and I live here for a while?
天啊
God.
-当然可以  -谢谢你
- Of course.  - Thank you.
你眉毛好奇怪
Your eyebrows look weird.
耶利米书是只牛蛙
"Jeremiah was a bullfrog.
它曾是我的好友
Was a good friend of mine,
它的话我不曾听懂
never understood a single word he said,
但我帮他喝了他的酒
but I helped him drink his wine."
所以不管怎样  你都会自摸
So you'll just touch yourself for anything, then?